# Durvesh K. Mundhe

8, Omkareshwar Ashish, Gajanan Nagar, Badlapur(East)

□ (+91) 8983707306 | ☑ durveshmundhe@gmail.com | 🏕 durveshmundhe.github.io | ☑ durveshmundhe | 💆 @is\_durvesh

## Summary\_\_\_

Working as Front End Developer in The Souled Store Pvt. Ltd. 2.3+ years experience in developing responsive User Interface. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools.

## Education\_

Bharati Vidyapeeth Institute of Management and Information Technology,	6.77 CGPA
Navi Mumbai	0.77 CGFA

MASTER IN COMPUTER APPLICATION 2015 - 2018

B. N. Bandodkar College of Science, Thane

Bachelors of Science (Information Technology) 2011 - 2014

**A.V.M. Jr. College, Badlapur**H.S.C.
2009 - 2011

I.E.S. Katrap Vidyalaya, Badlapur81.53%S.S.C.2009

# Work Experience\_\_\_\_\_

#### The Souled Store Pvt. Ltd.

Mumbai

5.07 CGPA

FRONT END DEVELOPER

August 2019 - Present

- Built reusable web components and flexible user interfaces using VueJS.
- Worked on Server Side Rendering project using NextJS to improve performance and SEO.
- Used BEM methodology for writing CSS.
- Implemented Front-End Analytics, helping the marketing team better understand the user engagement.
- Ownership of stylesheets and markup in projects; including but not limited to refactoring for performance and readability.

#### Tantra-Gyan Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

Mumbai

JR. SOFTWARE SOLUTIONS ENGINEER

July 2018 - July 2019

- REST APIs Integration to show dynamic content on website through CMS.
- Worked with Handlebars to create templates in the CRM product.
- Worked with React Library to develop Admin part of CMS.
- Made use of Lighthouse Auditing Tool to improve performance of website
- Use of Front-End tools such as npm, webpack.

#### Tantra-Gyan Technologies Pvt. Ltd

Mumbai

INTERN - SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Jan. 2018 - June 2018

- Utilized HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, ¡Query for website development.
- Made use of HighCharts Library to add interactive maps.
- Git for version control.
- On-Site SEO implementation.

### Skills

**Languagues** : JavaScript, Python

JS Libraries : jQuery, ReactJS, VueJS, NextJS

**CSS Framework** : Bootstrap, MaterialUI

**CSS Preprocessor** : SCSS

**Analytics** : Google Tag Manager, Google Analytics, CleverTap

**Database** : MySQL

# **Projects Undertaken**

#### Data Analysis and Visualization on Pro-Kabaddi League

Mini Project

3 months

PYTHON, NUMPY, PANDAS, MATPLOTLIB

- The analysis is done with Supervised Learning.
- Created a Deterministic Model using KNN, K-Means and Logistic Regression algorithms to find the accuracy.
- Visualization represents different aspects of the game in the graphical manner to aid understanding of data.

Dictionary App Mini Project

IONIC FRAMEWORK, ANGULARJS, WORDNIK API

2 months

- Dictionary App will allow to find meaning of words in just few seconds.
- It is developed in Ionic platform using AnjularJS and Wordnik API
- Facilitate English to English, English to Marathi and vice-versa meanings for the words.

Gaming Info Website Mini Project

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

2 months

• The main objective of website was to provide the information related to upcoming games across the different platforms.

## Extracurricular Activity \_\_\_\_\_

IIT Bombay

**PYTHON WORKSHOP** 

26th August 2017

Attended hands-on workshop on Python conducted by FOSSEE

B.V.I.M.I.T.

CONFERENCE June 29-30, 2017

• Attended National Conference on "Emerging Trends: Innovation & Challenges in Information Technology"